[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Did you ever feel when you were working so closely with this man that you would ever have to say the words you just said about him, that he is effectively an enemy combatant?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, I do to a degree.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Or do you believe that there should be a way of stopping him being able to use this as a platform to attack America, to attack American servicemen, and to potentially rally the enemy?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, I think the staff sergeant had it right that the judge was just doing her duty.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "From a legal standpoint is there anything that can be done to stop him turning this into a show trial?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Is expecting.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Who would you bet on?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I knew Tamerlan very well.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "How well did you know Tamerlan Tsarnaev and what changes did you see him go through?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "He had always been kind of, like John said, walked the line between clock cocky and arrogant.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "So you could see signs then that he was getting more aggressive perhaps?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "On the contrary, I never saw it coming.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "or had part of you always feared that he may be capable of not necessarily an atrocity like that but something bad?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Did you see any of that, either of you?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "That is correct.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Michael, there's also this connection to the triple homicide which happened on September 11, 2011, where once of the victims, Brendan Mess, also had a connection to the gym, is that right?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "That's what the authorities are saying.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "And the belief now is that Tamerlan may well have been involved in his murder and the murder of two others at the same time?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "I met her maybe two or three times.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Did you meet her?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Was he very much, as many have suggested, in his older brother's thrall?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "A young woman in her 30s went out to run an errand that any mother would at just before 3:00 in the morning and was never seen again alive.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "And what do you think has happened here?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "One, I would disagree with them because whenever there is a mother who leaves three children in such a gruesome and brutal way the local media will jump on it right away.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "What would you say to that?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Piers, I'm telling you, when I spoke with Sheriff Bouchard today, he said that they are, quote, \"dogging this case.\"", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "How is the investigation going into Rhonda's death?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I would never presume to tell a parent how they should feel or how they should emotionally react.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "But there's a point that if America saw the reality it could change things?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Does it help his party that he hasn't parachuted a Republican in here?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "He is certainly emerging -- well, in a general election absolutely.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Tell me, Margaret, I mean, is he already emerging as the compelling candidate to fight the next general election?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "-- in 2016 than it did in 2012.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What -- what could stop him?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Well, I mean -- there's this me amongst Republicans that all of his behavior will stop him now, by not appointing a Republican like Chris Smith, the New Jersey congressman, that won't stop him.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Well, what could stop him?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "But if they want to win -- Marc, if they want to win the election, isn't this what someone like him has to be doing?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "You know, I think parents -- both parents started working.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "How did America get so mediocre?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well, it's the stupid face on an important debate which is work-life balance.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "I mean, it's just an idiot thing to say, wasn't it, Margaret?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I think public opinion has been changed already just by knowing that those 6-year-olds, those babies were killed.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "If Americans saw the reality of a mass shooting outrage, could it change public opinion?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Here's the -- here's the difference, though, Piers.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "What he's saying is what will change the debate?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, I think first of all common decency is you have to defer to the parents.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Where do you draw the line there?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Days before the U.S. Supreme Court will rule on two important gay rights cases, the Dohmann case and the Prop 8 case about whether, you know, some of these laws will be overturned, you have, by the way, 120 -- 222 Republican legislators across the country have voted for freedom to marry, transgender, bisexual rights.", "docId": "130604pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Do these two stories today, two completely different stories, but joined if you like by the sense of, isn't it great that in modern America now, quite rapidly actually, we can celebrate both those things and it seems relatively normal?", "qSentId": 593}]